Guide to the Malaysia miscellany, 1977-2008.
Malaysia miscellany
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Malaysia miscellany, 1977-2008.
6516
.6 cubic ft.
Pamphlets, printed materials, and ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Brochures, booklets, political broadsides and published material relating to Malaysia.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Brochures, booklets, political broadsides and published material relating to Malaysia. Tourist brochures and pamphlets produced by the Tourist Development Corporation, Malaysia, Ministry of Culture and Tourism. Information brochure from the Inter Islamic University, Malaysia. Political broadsides, brochures, stickers and posters relating to the Malaysian election of 1999, including the Common Manifest of the Parti Islam Semalaysia, Partai Keadilan, Kertas Perintah and the Democratic Action Party.
This collection also contains programs, pamphlets, manifestos, buttons, stickers and flags from the political campaigns of 2004 and 2008. Campaign material is included from Barisan Nasional and its founding member UNMO, the Democratic Action Party (DAP), Islamic Party of Malaysia (PAS) and the collective Barisan Alternatif, consisting of Islamic Party of Malaysia (PAS), the Democratic Action Party (DAP), Malaysian People's Party (PRM), Parti Sosialis Malaysia (PSM), Malaysian Indian Congress (MIC), and People's Justice Party (PKR). It also includes a series of government issued booklets.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Democratic Action Party; Democratic Action Party.; Partai Keadilan; Partai Keadilan.; Partai Keadilan.; Parti Islam Semalaysia; Parti Islam Semalaysia.
Subjects:
Political science; Travel
Places:
Malaysia -- Description and travel.; Malaysia -- Politics and government.; Malaysia -- History.; Kuala Lumpur (Malaysia).; Kuching (Sarawak, Malaysia); Kelantan.; Selangor (Malaysia); Malaysia; Malaysia -- Kelantan; Malaysia -- Kuala Lumpur; Malaysia -- Kuching (Sarawak); Malaysia -- Selangor
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Brochures
  - Vital! A Smart Guide to Today's Woman, Vol. II. Malaysian AIDS Council., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - International Islamic University Malaysia, Penerangan Ringkas (Information Brochure), No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Buku Panduan Pengajian Asia Tenggara, Sessi 1997/98." Fakulti Sastra dan Sains Social, Universiti Malaya, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Informasi Pasar Keria." Proyek Informasi dan Perencanaan Tenage Kerja., 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Infoterra (Sistem Rujukan Antarbangsa untuk Sumber-Sumber Maklumat Mengenai Alam Sekitar -- International Referral System for sources of Environmental Information)." Kuala Lumpur: Malaysia Infoterra NFP., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Kelantan, Map and Guide." Tourist Development Corporation Malaysia, Ministry of Culture and Tourism., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Kuala Lumpur Guide." Tourist Development Corporation Malaysia, Ministry of Culture and Tourism, No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Malaysia, A General Guide." Malaysia Tourism Promotion Board, Ministry of Culture, Arts and Tourism., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Malaysia, A General Guide, Edition 1991." Malaysia tourism Promotion Board, Ministry of Culture, Arts and Tourism., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Selangor Darul Ehsan, Map and Guide." Tourist Development Corporation of Malaysia, Ministry of Culture, Arts and Tourism., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Tarman, Wayne and Mike Reed. The Official Kuching Guide 1996" TLCS Consultants., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Visit Malaysia Year '94: The Traveller's Guide to Malaysia's Fascinating Treatsures." Malaysia Tourism Promotion Board., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Malaysis." BOAC (British Overseas Airways Corporation) 1967., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Malaysia's Hill Resorts." Department of Tourism, Ministry of Commerce and Industry., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Kelantan--Tradition Recapture." Malaysian Handicraft Development Corporation Kelantan Branch., No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Pre-2004 Election Materials
  - Pin. Ke Arah Reformasi Tulen, PRM, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pocket Calendar: Salam Perjuangan, Keadilan untuk Semua, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sticker: Keadilan, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Do We Need an Opposition?, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Pilihlah Barisan Alternatif, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: NO DAM. S.O.S. Selangor, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Petikan Ucapan Dasar Muktamar PAS 1999 (in Chinese characters), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Partai Rakyat Malaysia (PRM) (in Chinese characters), No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Turutilah Mereka Menolak Barisan Nasional, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Dr. Syed Husin Ali, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flier: Cuba Kami untuk Tahun, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet: Beware of MCA/Gerakan "Islamic State" Trump Card, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet: Towards a Just Malaysia, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet: Democratic Action Party, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet: Manifesto/Dasar Gerakan Mahasiswa Lantang Negara (GMLN), No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Petikan Manifesto BN: Kebebasan Berpolitik kepada Semua Rakyat, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Jangan Biarkan Mereka Menipu Kita…Undilah PAS, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Malaysia Deserves Better, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Plastic banner: Democratic Action Party, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Jangan Sia-Siakan Hak Anda, Pilihlah Keadilan, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Undilah Keadilan, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 2004-2008 Election Materials
  - Barisan Nasional (1), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Programs, pamphlets and a button. Also a sticker and pen from UNMO, its founding member.
  - Barisan Alternatif, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Program, pamphlet, poster, manifestos and a keychain. Barisan Alternatif consists of Islamic Party of Malaysia (PAS), the Democratic Action Party (DAP), Malaysian People's Party (PRM) and People's Justice Party (PKR)
  - Democratic Action Party (1), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Posters, program, cartoons, manifesto, stickers, flag and plastic bag
  - Islamic Party of Malaysia (1), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Poster, manifesto, sticker, flags and newspapers
  - Miscellaneous (1), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Newspaper and booklets related to the political campaigns of 2004
  - Educational flyers, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Flyers to educate voters on the election process and motivate them to vote
  - Democratic Action Party (2), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Program and pamphlets
  - Parti Sosialis Malaysia, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Islamic Party of Malaysia (2), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Manifesto, flyer and photoalbum
  - Malaysian Indian Congress, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Agenda and "Priorities and Strategies" booklet
  - Barisan Nasional (2), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Manifesto, flyer and candidate description of T. Mohan
  - People's Justice Party, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Newspaper article, pamphlets and flyers
  - Miscellaneous (2), 2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Pamphlet Barisan Alternatif, flyer with photos of sleeping politicians, pamphlet "Adun vs Rakyat", pamphlet "Menggamit Memori Perjuangan", newspaper "Suara Mahasiswa"; edition February 2008
  - Transformasi Milayah Utara siri pengetahuan am, 2007-10 (Box 2)
    Booklet, published by Jabatan P.Enerangan Malaysia
  - Media: Memahat Sejarah Membina Tamadun, 2007-06-28 (Box 2)
  - Penjelasan Mengenai Subsidi Dan Bantuan Kerajaan Kepada Rakyat, 2008-02 (Box 2)
  - The Malaysian Public Services Commitments 2008 - Tan Sri Mohd Sidek Hassan, 2008-02 (Box 2)
  - Indeks Harga Pengguna, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Menjana Pembangunan Wilayah Timur, 2007-12 (Box 2)
  - Sukan Tuntut Komitmen Total: Kerajaan Kota Janji, 2008-02 (Box 2)
    Booklet, published by Jabatan P.Enerangan Malaysia, including stories surrounding the 2006 Asian Games
  - Belia & Wanita: aspirasi negara, 2008-02 (Box 2)
  - Button Undilah Barisan Nasional, 2004; MU-1562 (Box 3)
    Button
  - T-shirt ADIL, 2004; MU-1563 (Box 3)
    Text on shirt: "Ke Arah Reformasi - ADIL"
  - Paper flag Islamic Party of Malaysia, 2004; MU-1564 (Box 3)
  - Textile flag Islamic Party of Malaysia, 2004; MU-1565 (Box 3)
  - Textile car flag Democratic Action Party, Undated; MU-1566 (Box 3)
  - Plastic bag Democratic Action Party, Undated; MU-1567 (Box 3)
  - 4-color pen Puteri UMNO, Undated; MU-1568 (Box 3)
  - Key-cord Barisan Alternatif, Undated; MU-1569 (Box 3)